<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GlobeQuiz</string>

    <string name="log_tag">globequiz</string>

    <string name="version">Version 1.14</string>

    <string name="single_player">Start Game</string>
    <string name="multi_player">Multiplayer</string>
    <string name="globe_button_label">Globe</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="start_single_player">Start game</string>
    <string name="select_questions">Select Questions</string>
    <string name="select_regions">Select Regions</string>
    <string name="number_of_questions">Number of Questions</string>

    <string name="logo_description">Logo showing pictogram of a globe</string>
    <string name="map_description">Map indicating the location of the country</string>

    <string name="level_too_low_format">You have to reach level %d to select this option.</string>

    <string name="progress_format">%1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="too_many_countries_format">Selected continents contain only %d countries</string>
    <string name="select_a_question">Select at least one question</string>
    <string name="select_a_region">Select at least one region</string>

    <string name="next_question">Next question</string>
    <string name="next_country">Next country</string>
    <string name="next_score">Show score</string>
    <string name="not_enough_questions">Sorry, there are no questions of these types for the selected continents.</string>

    <string name="score_label">Score</string>
    <string name="back_to_menu">Menu</string>

    <string name="score_number_format">%1$d of %2$d answers correct - %3$.02f%%</string>
    <string name="score_experience_gained_format">%1$d XP earned</string>
    <string name="score_experience_format">%1$d of %2$d XP to level %3$d</string>

    <string name="player_name_format">Player: %1$s</string>
    <string name="player_experience_format">"Level %1$d - %2$d/%3$d XP</string>

    <string name="evaluation1">Did you even try?</string>
    <string name="evaluation2">You can tell east from west</string>
    <string name="evaluation3">Average</string>
    <string name="evaluation4">Quite good</string>
    <string name="evaluation5">Impressive</string>
    <string name="evaluation6">Flawless</string>

    <string name="abort_game_warning">End the game?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>

    <string name="please_enter_name">Please enter a name.</string>
    <string name="player_already_exists">The player name already exists. Please enter another name.</string>

    <string name="select_player">Select Player</string>
    <string name="create_player">Create Player</string>
    <string name="enter_player_name">Player name:</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>
    <string name="default_player_name">GeoWizz9000</string>

    <string name="remove_player_warning">Do you really want to delete player %1$s and loose all progress?</string>
    <string name="language">Language:</string>
    <string name="language_flag_description">Picture of a flag</string>

    <string name="select_player_button">Change player</string>

    <string name="wiki_button_description">Opens Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="info_format">%1$s\nCapital: %2$s</string>
    <string name="info_format_no_capital">%1$s</string>
    <string name="about_button">About</string>
    <string name="license_text_label">Licenses</string>
    <string name="author_text_label">by Thorsten Schimannek</string>
    <string name="email_text_label">globequiz.contact@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="libpng_license_formatted" translatable="false"><![CDATA[
COPYRIGHT NOTICE, DISCLAIMER, and LICENSE<br>
=========================================<br>
<br>
PNG Reference Library License version 2<br>
---------------------------------------<br>
<br>
 * Copyright (c) 1995-2019 The PNG Reference Library Authors.<br>
 * Copyright (c) 2018-2019 Cosmin Truta.<br>
 * Copyright (c) 2000-2002, 2004, 2006-2018 Glenn Randers-Pehrson.<br>
 * Copyright (c) 1996-1997 Andreas Dilger.<br>
 * Copyright (c) 1995-1996 Guy Eric Schalnat, Group 42, Inc.<br>
<br>
The software is supplied "as is", without warranty of any kind, express or implied, including, without limitation, the warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title, and non-infringement.  In no event shall the Copyright owners, or anyone distributing the software, be liable for any damages or other liability, whether in contract, tort or otherwise, arising from, out of, or in connection with the software, or the use or other dealings in the software, even if advised of the possibility of such damage.<br>
<br>
Permission is hereby granted to use, copy, modify, and distribute this software, or portions hereof, for any purpose, without fee, subject to the following restrictions:<br>
<br>
 1. The origin of this software must not be misrepresented; you must not claim that you wrote the original software.  If you use this software in a product, an acknowledgment in the product documentation would be appreciated, but is not required.<br>
<br>
 2. Altered source versions must be plainly marked as such, and must not be misrepresented as being the original software.<br>
<br>
 3. This Copyright notice may not be removed or altered from any source or altered source distribution.<br>
<br>
<br>
PNG Reference Library License version 1 (for libpng 0.5 through 1.6.35)<br>
-----------------------------------------------------------------------<br>
<br>
libpng versions 1.0.7, July 1, 2000, through 1.6.35, July 15, 2018 are Copyright (c) 2000-2002, 2004, 2006-2018 Glenn Randers-Pehrson, are derived from libpng-1.0.6, and are distributed according to the same disclaimer and license as libpng-1.0.6 with the following individuals added to the list of Contributing Authors:<br>
<br>
    Simon-Pierre Cadieux<br>
    Eric S. Raymond<br>
    Mans Rullgard<br>
    Cosmin Truta<br>
    Gilles Vollant<br>
    James Yu<br>
    Mandar Sahastrabuddhe<br>
    Google Inc.<br>
    Vadim Barkov<br>
<br>
and with the following additions to the disclaimer:<br>
<br>
    There is no warranty against interference with your enjoyment of the library or against infringement.  There is no warranty that our efforts or the library will fulfill any of your particular purposes or needs.  This library is provided with all faults, and the entire risk of satisfactory quality, performance, accuracy, and effort is with the user.<br>
<br>
Some files in the "contrib" directory and some configure-generated files that are distributed with libpng have other copyright owners, and are released under other open source licenses.<br>
<br>
libpng versions 0.97, January 1998, through 1.0.6, March 20, 2000, are Copyright (c) 1998-2000 Glenn Randers-Pehrson, are derived from libpng-0.96, and are distributed according to the same disclaimer and license as libpng-0.96, with the following individuals added to the list of Contributing Authors:<br>
<br>
    Tom Lane<br>
    Glenn Randers-Pehrson<br>
    Willem van Schaik<br>
<br>
libpng versions 0.89, June 1996, through 0.96, May 1997, are Copyright (c) 1996-1997 Andreas Dilger, are derived from libpng-0.88, and are distributed according to the same disclaimer and license as libpng-0.88, with the following individuals added to the list of Contributing Authors:<br>
<br>
    John Bowler<br>
    Kevin Bracey<br>
    Sam Bushell<br>
    Magnus Holmgren<br>
    Greg Roelofs<br>
    Tom Tanner<br>
<br>
Some files in the "scripts" directory have other copyright owners, but are released under this license.<br>
<br>
libpng versions 0.5, May 1995, through 0.88, January 1996, are Copyright (c) 1995-1996 Guy Eric Schalnat, Group 42, Inc.<br>
<br>
For the purposes of this copyright and license, "Contributing Authors" is defined as the following set of individuals:<br>
<br>
    Andreas Dilger<br>
    Dave Martindale<br>
    Guy Eric Schalnat<br>
    Paul Schmidt<br>
    Tim Wegner<br>
<br>
The PNG Reference Library is supplied "AS IS".  The Contributing Authors and Group 42, Inc. disclaim all warranties, expressed or implied, including, without limitation, the warranties of merchantability and of fitness for any purpose.  The Contributing Authors and Group 42, Inc. assume no liability for direct, indirect, incidental, special, exemplary, or consequential damages, which may result from the use of the PNG Reference Library, even if advised of the possibility of such damage.<br>
<br>
Permission is hereby granted to use, copy, modify, and distribute this source code, or portions hereof, for any purpose, without fee, subject to the following restrictions:<br>
<br>
 1. The origin of this source code must not be misrepresented.<br>
<br>
 2. Altered versions must be plainly marked as such and must not be misrepresented as being the original source.<br>
<br>
 3. This Copyright notice may not be removed or altered from any source or altered source distribution.<br>
<br>
The Contributing Authors and Group 42, Inc. specifically permit, without fee, and encourage the use of this source code as a component to supporting the PNG file format in commercial products.  If you use this source code in a product, acknowledgment is not required but would be appreciated.<br>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="happy_bunny_formatted" translatable="false"><![CDATA[
    <b>OpenGL Mathematics (GLM)</b><br>
    GLM is licensed under The Happy Bunny License and MIT License<br>
    <br>
    <b>The Happy Bunny License<br>(Modified MIT License)</b><br>
    Copyright (c) 2005 - 2014 G-Truc Creation<br>
    <br>
    Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:<br>
    <br>
    The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.<br>
    <br>
    Restrictions:<br>
    By making use of the Software for military purposes, you choose to make a Bunny unhappy.<br>
    <br>
    THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.<br>
    <br>
    <b>The MIT License</b><br>
    Copyright (c) 2005 - 2014 G-Truc Creation<br>
    <br>
    Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:<br>
    <br>
    The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.<br>
    <br>
    THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
]]></string>
    <string name="common_codecs_license_formatted" translatable="false"><![CDATA[
<p style="text-align:center">
<strong>Apache License<br></br>Version 2.0, January 2004<br></br></strong>
<strong><a href="http://www.apache.org/licenses/">http://www.apache.org/licenses/</a></strong>
</p>
<br>
<p>TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION</p>
<br>
<p><strong><a name="definitions">1. Definitions</a></strong>.</p>

<div style="margin-left: 1em;">

  <p>"<strong>License</strong>" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and
distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.</p>
<br>
  <p>"<strong>Licensor</strong>" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the
copyright owner that is granting the License.</p>
<br>
  <p>"<strong>Legal Entity</strong>" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other
entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with
that entity. For the purposes of this definition, "<strong>control</strong>" means (i) the
power, direct or indirect, to cause the direction or management of such
entity, whether by contract or otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty
percent (50%) or more of the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial
ownership of such entity.</p>
<br>
  <p>"<strong>You</strong>" (or "<strong>Your</strong>") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising
permissions granted by this License.</p>
<br>
  <p>"<strong>Source</strong>" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,
including but not limited to software source code, documentation source,
and configuration files.</p>
<br>
  <p>"<strong>Object</strong>" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation
or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to compiled
object code, generated documentation, and conversions to other media types.</p>

  <p>"<strong>Work</strong>" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or Object form,
made available under the License, as indicated by a copyright notice that
is included in or attached to the work (an example is provided in the
Appendix below).</p>
<br>
  <p>"<strong>Derivative Works</strong>" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object form,
that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the editorial
revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications represent, as
a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes of this License,
Derivative Works shall not include works that remain separable from, or
merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative
Works thereof.</p>
<br>
  <p>"<strong>Contribution</strong>" shall mean any work of authorship, including the original
version of the Work and any modifications or additions to that Work or
Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally submitted to Licensor for
inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner or by an individual or Legal
Entity authorized to submit on behalf of the copyright owner. For the
purposes of this definition, "<strong>submitted</strong>" means any form of electronic,
verbal, or written communication sent to the Licensor or its
representatives, including but not limited to communication on electronic
mailing lists, source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that
are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose of discussing
and improving the Work, but excluding communication that is conspicuously
marked or otherwise designated in writing by the copyright owner as "<strong>Not a
Contribution.</strong>"</p>
<br>
  <p>"<strong>Contributor</strong>" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity on
behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and
subsequently incorporated within the Work.</p>
<br>
</div>
<br>
<p><strong><a name="copyright">2. Grant of Copyright License</a></strong>. Subject to the
terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You
a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly
display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the Work and such
Derivative Works in Source or Object form.</p>
<br>
<p><strong><a name="patent">3. Grant of Patent License</a></strong>. Subject to the terms
and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a
perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made, use,
offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work, where such
license applies only to those patent claims licensable by such Contributor
that are necessarily infringed by their Contribution(s) alone or by
combination of their Contribution(s) with the Work to which such
Contribution(s) was submitted. If You institute patent litigation against
any entity (including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging
that the Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes
direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses
granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate as of the
date such litigation is filed.</p>
<br>
<p><strong><a name="redistribution">4. Redistribution</a></strong>. You may reproduce and
distribute copies of the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium,
with or without modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that
You meet the following conditions:</p>
<br>
<ol style="list-style: lower-latin;">
<li>You must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative Works a
copy of this License; and</li>
<br>
<li>You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices stating
that You changed the files; and</li>
<br>
<li>You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works that You
distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution notices from
the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices that do not pertain to
any part of the Derivative Works; and</li>
<br>
<li>If the Work includes a "<strong>NOTICE</strong>" text file as part of its distribution,
then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a readable copy
of the attribution notices contained within such NOTICE file, excluding
those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in
at least one of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed
as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation,
if provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display generated
by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party notices normally
appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only
and do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution notices
within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to
the NOTICE text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution
notices cannot be construed as modifying the License.
<br/>
<br/>
You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and may
provide additional or different license terms and conditions for use,
reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or for any such
Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use, reproduction, and
distribution of the Work otherwise complies with the conditions stated in
this License.
</li>
<br>
</ol>
<br>
<p><strong><a name="contributions">5. Submission of Contributions</a></strong>. Unless You
explicitly state otherwise, any Contribution intentionally submitted for
inclusion in the Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and
conditions of this License, without any additional terms or conditions.
Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify the
terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed with Licensor
regarding such Contributions.</p>
<br>
<p><strong><a name="trademarks">6. Trademarks</a></strong>. This License does not grant
permission to use the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product
names of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary use
in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the
NOTICE file.</p>
<br>
<p><strong><a name="no-warranty">7. Disclaimer of Warranty</a></strong>. Unless required by
applicable law or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and
each Contributor provides its Contributions) on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT
WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied, including,
without limitation, any warranties or conditions of TITLE,
NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You
are solely responsible for determining the appropriateness of using or
redistributing the Work and assume any risks associated with Your exercise
of permissions under this License.</p>
<br>
<p><strong><a name="no-liability">8. Limitation of Liability</a></strong>. In no event and
under no legal theory, whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or
otherwise, unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and
grossly negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be
liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,
incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a result
of this License or out of the use or inability to use the Work (including
but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill, work stoppage, computer
failure or malfunction, or any and all other commercial damages or losses),
even if such Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such
damages.</p>
<br>
<p><strong><a name="additional">9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability</a></strong>.
While redistributing the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose
to offer, and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,
or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this License.
However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only on Your own behalf
and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf of any other Contributor,
and only if You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor
harmless for any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such
Contributor by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional
liability.</p>
</div>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="achievement">Achievement</string>
    <string name="next_achievement">Next</string>
    <string name="show_achievements">Show</string>
    <string name="achievements_earned">You unlocked %1$d achievements!</string>
    <string name="achievements_list">Achievements</string>
    <string name="show_relief">Show relief:</string>
</resources>
